resultinbd.net 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting our website **ResultinBD.Net.** At **ResultinBD.Net** , The privacy of our visitors are extreme importance to us. All of you have to follow and read our Privacy Policy before to use. The publisher takes the protection of your personal data and information very sincerely. Your data or information will be protected under the law. See the articles to learn more about our ( **ResultinBD.Net** ) Privacy Policies.

We ( **ResultinBD.Net)** publish all information for the benefits of visitors. You can visit our website without disclosing your information to us. Every access and collection of all information to our website and each download of a file on the website is logged in our local server. The storage serves internal system-related and statistical purposes and internet marketing. Be recorded: the name of the Internet service provider, the website from which you are visiting us and the pages that you visit, the name of the file, date and day, time, amount of data transferred, notification of successful download file or data, web browser, accessing domain and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the requesting computer. You as a user, remain anonymous.

**Information collection**

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also keep your information like your browser name, operating system name and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

**Security of you personal Information**

**ResultinBD.Net** is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to optimize the delivery of advertising on the websites they are visit. Please note that it’s not possible in any case to include your full name, contact address or other personal details, either from your community center, the cookies used on your interests or not. You can of course still use **ResultinBD.Net** , if you have disallowed the use of cookies in your browser settings. To post comments or give suggestion and contribute in voting, you must also accept the use of cookies.

**External Links**

Our website contains links to other websites such as any official website. You will find links on our pages that refer to pages of third (3rd) parties. The publisher Nuremberg press has no influence on whether their operators comply with the data protection regulations.

**Use of Social Plugins**

**ResultinBD.Net** used so-called social plugins of the social network facebook.com, recordable as the; Like button and share button. Facebook.com is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plugins are marked with the Facebook logo.

When you visit a page of **Resultinbd** which contains such features, your browser to establishes a direct connection to the servers of Facebook for Like and share button. Certain data available in the user’s Web browser from the computer of the user are transmitted to Facebook and Facebook sent back content. The contents are moved by Facebook directly to your browser which embeds the latter into the website.  **ResultinBD.Net** has no influence on the amount of data that Facebook collects with this plugin.

**Acceptance of Terms/ Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Using **ResultinBD.Net** will assume that you accept the privacy policy of this site. When we use any third party for any affiliated service, the third party privacy policy also applicable to you by using this site.

If you have any question or concerns, feel free to contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
